TSZ WAI "JASMINE" WONG

Austin TX 78753 | (832) 573-5932 | jaswong4497@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/tsz-wai-wong

CAREER PROFILE

The University of Texas at Austin graduate with a Bachelor of Science in Kinesiology and Health and a Business minor. Held various jobs and internship in Spain and the U.S with 3 years' experience in client communication. Served on several university organization. High knowledge of logistics and resource management through 6 years of studying and working abroad. Built additional leadership capabilities including strong communication and integrity via volunteering efforts.

EDUCATION

The University of Texas at Austin Bachelor of Science in Kinesiology and Health, Minor in Business Spring 2019

WORK EXPERIENCE

Boys and Girls Club at Austin Area - Coordinator of Academic Success at Cook Elementary School

Mar 2019 - present

- Coach 46 students in developing their communication and team building skills through creative activities like 'Finger Math'
- Boost academic results in 90% of students by providing weekly one-on-one mentor sessions to set academic and personal goals
- Orchestrated a series of Anger Management Workshop to help 10+ students who struggle with emotions and behaviors
- Incorporate fun and collaborative group activities to encourage fitness and healthy lifestyle

Longhorn Foundation - Football Game Day Touchdown Club Manager

Aug - Dec 2017, 2018

- Delivered excellent customer service to 1000+ donors during game-days as their point of contact
- Enhanced customer satisfaction by 60% through active listening and reduced time to answer customer inquiries by 50%
- Solved unexpected problems such as unauthorized personnel and medical emergencies in a fast-paced environment
- · Communicated complex logistic inquiries to vendors, donors, and staff in a professional and supportive demeanor

The University of Texas at Austin - Teaching Assistant

Aug 2018 - Dec 2018

- Fostered an accepting environment for students to learn from their mistakes and turn them into new variations
- Influenced students to appreciate partner dancing and reinforced a respectful and supportive community

Global Performance, Barcelona, Spain - Athletic Training & Rehabilitation Research Intern

May 2017 - Aug 2017

- Demonstrated the ability to overcome frequent ambiguity through working in a foreign country
- Assembled recovery programs for professional athletes, 60+ hours hands-on rehabilitation experience on injured athletes

Project SEED, The University of Texas at Austin - Research Assistant

Oct 2017 - Mar 2018

- Analyzed the stress response of Mexican American Children who translate for their parents regularly
- · Held presentations across campus to a broad way of audiences on the results of our findings

Texas Midland Management and Realty - Dun Huang Plaza Management Assistant

May 2015 - Sept 2015

- Oversaw administrative work for 100+ businesses including leasing/selling contracts with vendors
- Built rapport with owners, tenants, vendors, workers, board committees and active members of the plaza

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

UT Austin Campus Event+Entertainment - "Try Culture" Event Coordinator

Aug 2018 - Dec 2018

- Cultivated a team of 50 to coordinate a successful campus event with 800+ participants
- Exposed students to Asian, Mexican, and African culture, languages, and history through performances and activities

LeaderShape Institute (May 2018 cohort)

May 2018

- · Demonstrated leadership skills through team building and problem solving challenges with a group of 20 attendees
- Planned social events with 30+ attendees, taught salsa and bachata classes

Hong Kong Woman Basketball Team, Captain

2010 - 2013

- Led a team of 16 professional players to compete and won 3 Championships
- Strengthened team communication through weekly meetings and positively motivated teammates on and off the court

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

MULTI LINGUIST: English, Cantonese, Mandarin (All fluent in reading, writing, and speaking)

INTERESTS: Social Dance (Country two-step, Swing, Kizomba), AcroYoga, Self-awareness